<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>SupportDesk BV - Populair Feed</title>
		<description>Magento en Joomla support nodig?</description>
		<link>http://localhost</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost/feed-populair.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      
    <item>
      <title>Mage.coach - The online Magento Performance tool</title>
      
        <dc:creator>Mats van de Seijp</dc:creator>
      
      
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;box__image&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a title=&quot;Mage.coach - The online Magento Performance tool&quot; href=&quot;/2017/04/02/mage-coach-the-online-magento-performance-tool/&quot;&gt;
    &lt;amp-img noloading height=200 width=188 alt=&quot;Mage.coach - The online Magento Performance tool&quot; attribution=&quot;Mage.coach - The online Magento Performance tool&quot; layout=responsive src=&quot;/img/news/penguin_report.svg&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we sat down with &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost/over-ons/ray-bogman&quot;&gt;Ray Bogman&lt;/a&gt;, inventor of &lt;a href=&quot;https://mage.coach/&quot;&gt;Mage.coach&lt;/a&gt; for some more information about this new tool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Who is Ray and what is Mage.coach?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ray Bogman is the &lt;span class=&quot;underline&quot;&gt;co-founder&lt;/span&gt; and&lt;span class=&quot;underline&quot;&gt; technical director&lt;/span&gt; of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.supportdesk.nu/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;SupportDesk.nu&lt;/a&gt; and regular spokesperson at many &lt;strong&gt;Magento&lt;/strong&gt; events around the world. &lt;strong&gt;Mage.coach&lt;/strong&gt; is a tool that analyses the &lt;strong&gt;performance, accessibility, usability&lt;/strong&gt; of&lt;strong&gt; Magento websites.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How did you come up with the idea?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For about 8 years I am interested in all theory about &lt;strong&gt;website performances&lt;/strong&gt;, and how to enhance them. &lt;br&gt;I came up with the idea of &lt;strong&gt;Mage.coach&lt;/strong&gt; after stumbling on a problem for several years and decided to do something about it. When I used to analyze the performances of websites I couldn't find tools that fitted my needs. When I discovered &lt;strong&gt;Sitespeed.io&lt;/strong&gt; I got inspired on what was possible with open source tools and began designing my own analyzing tool. The concept was to design a product that makes website analyses generic and easy. So&lt;strong&gt; Mage.coach&lt;/strong&gt; is a tool in which you can simply &lt;strong&gt;analyze&lt;/strong&gt; the &lt;strong&gt;performance&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;Magento&lt;/strong&gt; websites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;A little bit more specific about Mage.coach&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We build &lt;strong&gt;Mage.Coach&lt;/strong&gt; around the open source software of Sitespeed.io and started tweaking, changing and adding some extra functionalities. The concept is to make analyses easy, so imagine if you want to check how good your website performs, you only have to take 4 small steps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;check&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://mage.coach/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;mage Coach&quot;&gt;Mage.coach&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fill in the URL of the website you want to analyze&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fill in info (browser type, device type, and connection type)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click start and our tool will send you a report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The report will give you an insight in your;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;check&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overal performance of the website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usability of the website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accessibility of the website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;insight on how to enhance the SEO of the website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Can you only use Mage.Coach for Magento websites?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, you can use this tool for every website. But the idea for &lt;strong&gt;Mage.coach&lt;/strong&gt; is to make a &lt;strong&gt;plug-in system&lt;/strong&gt; in which we write specific plug-ins to check specific &lt;strong&gt;Magento 1&lt;/strong&gt; and&lt;strong&gt; Magento 2&lt;/strong&gt; website features. So you can use the tool for every website but the generated advises are made specific for Magento websites, hence the name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Since its an open source program, what's the business model?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no business model. Sitespeed.io and Magento are both open source programs. Open source software communities mostly depend on voluntary contributions, so this is my way to give something back to the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Are there already similar concepts?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The program is based on Sitespeed.io so, in a way, it is not original. But if you look at what the tool contributes, specifically on &lt;strong&gt;SEO&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;usability&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;accessibility&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;Magento 1&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt; websites, it is original.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Where do you see Mage.coach in 1 year?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The official launch of &lt;strong&gt;Mage.coach&lt;/strong&gt; will be held on &lt;span class=&quot;underline&quot;&gt;April 3rd&lt;/span&gt; during the &lt;strong&gt;Magento Imagine&lt;/strong&gt; event at &lt;strong&gt;Las Vegas&lt;/strong&gt;. Then we go from Private Beta to Public Beta. With the feedback we get from some experts at the event we hope to get the tool from public Beta to fully operational.&lt;br&gt;So Next year, hopefully, The &lt;strong&gt;Mage.coach&lt;/strong&gt; is fully operational, most of our Magento user will know us and we will be busy writing a lot of plugins to make analyzing specific &lt;strong&gt;Magento&lt;/strong&gt; parts easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Where do you see Mage.coach in 3 years?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mage.coach is fully functional and we have a large set of plugins for our customers so they can easily get in-depth insights into their &lt;strong&gt;website performances&lt;/strong&gt;. I also think Magento will have a &lt;strong&gt;headless&lt;/strong&gt; environment, so it will only work at the backend of the website. In this case, &lt;strong&gt;Mage.coach&lt;/strong&gt; can help website owners optimizing their front-end by selecting the right codes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you want to know more about &lt;a href=&quot;https://mage.coach/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Mage.Coach&quot;&gt;Mage.Coach&lt;/a&gt; ? Don't hesitate to contact &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost/over-ons/ray-bogman&quot; title=&quot;Ray Bogman&quot;&gt;Ray Bogman&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://localhost/2017/04/02/mage-coach-the-online-magento-performance-tool/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost/2017/04/02/mage-coach-the-online-magento-performance-tool/</guid>
      
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          <a title="Mage.coach - The online Magento Performance tool" href="http://localhost/2017/04/02/mage-coach-the-online-magento-performance-tool/">
            <img alt="Mage.coach - The online Magento Performance tool" src="http://localhost/img/news/penguin_report.svg" />
          </a>
        ]]>
      </content>
      
    </item>
  
    <item>
      <title>Magento 1.8 'form_keys' impact on FPC</title>
      
        <dc:creator>Melvyn Sopacua</dc:creator>
      
      
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;Magento 1.8 Form Keys&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the beginning of time Magento's backend contained a form key that protected against XSS attacks [1]. With &lt;strong&gt;Magento 1.8&lt;/strong&gt; the form key has entered the frontend for pretty much the same reason: to protect against form submission from another website, using your browser. A malicious attacker can add stuff to your cart while you're in a different browser tab or even complete an order for you. This relies on predictable URLs, because the site will not have access to the actual HTML content in the browser tab where you have your Magento order waiting. Everything sent to the Magento store will however submit your cookies and thus use your session.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Enter the form key&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By adding a unique key to each form or to each link that generates an action on the server, the URL or form content becomes no longer predictable. The form key is stored in the session data and validated upon submission to the server. If they don't match - you get a form key error and the action is not completed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way it is implemented in Magento 1.8 is not straight-forward for most of the &lt;strong&gt;Magento FPC implementations&lt;/strong&gt; out there and will generate form key errors, because by default they will cache the pages containing the form key of the user that first requested the page and caused it to be stored in the full page cache.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Magento frontend implementation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, the form key is not a separate block which can be excluded from FPC. And to make things worse, it's part of top level pages you will want to cache, like categories and product detail and even the homepage if it contains &quot;add to cart&quot; links (which most homepages out there do). For an example, take a look at &lt;strong&gt;app/design/frontend/base/default/template/catalog/product/list.phtml&lt;/strong&gt;. You will notice several calls to &lt;strong&gt;$this-&amp;gt;getAddToCartUrl()&lt;/strong&gt; which is defined in &lt;strong&gt;app/code/core/Mage/Catalog/Block/Product/Abstract.php&lt;/strong&gt;. In there you'll see that unconditionally, the form_key is added to the URL parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, using a separate block that would allow FPC implementors to mark it dynamic, would incur a heavy performance penalty, because every link that contains a form_key or form that contains a form_key input element, would have delays for loading and executing the block from a separate file and effectively only outputs sixteen characters fetched from the user's session data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;But here's the good part&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The good thing is, that a solid FPC implementation should also have code to replace the session ID that is output in some pages with the actual session ID from the currently viewing user. This code can be expanded with a replacement for the form key and this is exactly how Magento Enterprise is doing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a cacheable page is stored in the FPC container, one replaces the form key with a placeholder. After retrieving the stored HTML and before serving the cached page, the placeholder is restored with the form key stored in the user's session or if one does not exist, one should be generated (and subsequently stored in the user's session).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pages that receive the form key should in general not be cached or at least (partly) tailor to the current user (&quot;dynamic blocks&quot;). This is where the validation code will be called and when done right should no longer generate form key errors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Update&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We know of the following FPC implementations who have patched their code:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;check&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;Information about Lesti FPC&quot; href=&quot;http://gordonlesti.com/lestifpc/&quot;&gt;Lesti FPC&lt;/a&gt; as of &lt;a title=&quot;Fix for 1.8 Form key&quot; href=&quot;https://github.com/GordonLesti/Lesti_Fpc/commit/e3725928fcac1924ed663c33bd4067e99b3e7eb1&quot;&gt;this commit &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a title=&quot;Information about Extendware Full Page Cache&quot; href=&quot;http://www.extendware.com/magento-extensions/performance/full-page-cache-magento-extension.html&quot;&gt;Extendware Full Page Cache&lt;/a&gt;, version 1.6.8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are the maintainer of an FPC implementation or know that an implementation is fixed or not affected, feel free to provide me the details and we'll update the list as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference:&lt;br&gt;[1] &lt;a href=&quot;http://net.tutsplus.com/tutorials/php/secure-your-forms-with-form-keys/&quot;&gt;http://net.tutsplus.com/tutorials/php/secure-your-forms-with-form-keys/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://net.tutsplus.com/tutorials/php/secure-your-forms-with-form-keys/&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://localhost/2013/10/11/magento-1-8-form-keys-impact-on-fpc/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost/2013/10/11/magento-1-8-form-keys-impact-on-fpc/</guid>
      
    </item>
  
    <item>
      <title>Keystone Magento 2 Magento 2 Cookbook door Ray Bogman en Vladimir Kerkhof</title>
      
        <dc:creator>Hiltje Conradi</dc:creator>
      
      
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;box__image&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a title=&quot;Keystone Magento 2 Magento 2 Cookbook door Ray Bogman en Vladimir Kerkhof&quot; href=&quot;/2016/03/14/keystone-magento-2-magento-2-cookbook-door-ray-bogman-en-vladimir-kerkhof/&quot;&gt;
    &lt;amp-img noloading height=344 width=278 alt=&quot;Keystone Magento 2 Magento 2 Cookbook door Ray Bogman en Vladimir Kerkhof&quot; attribution=&quot;Keystone Magento 2 Magento 2 Cookbook door Ray Bogman en Vladimir Kerkhof&quot; layout=responsive src=&quot;/img/news/mage2cookbook-small.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Begin april 2016&lt;/strong&gt; is het zover: het boek &quot;&lt;strong&gt;Magento 2 Cookbook&lt;/strong&gt;&quot; geschreven door &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost/over-ons/ray-bogman&quot; title=&quot;Ray Bogman&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ray Bogman&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (CTO &amp;amp; co-founder &lt;strong&gt;SupportDesk B.V.&lt;/strong&gt;) en conculega &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost/over-ons/vladimir-kerkhoff&quot; title=&quot;Vladimir Kerkhof&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vladimir Kerkhof&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; zal gepubliceerd worden. Het boek bevat meer dan 400 bladzijdes en 50 praktische Magento 2 &quot;recepten&quot; die zullen helpen om de volle potentie van Magento te benutten met als doel een professionele webshop te bouwen. Het is geschreven voor Magento gebruikers (&lt;strong&gt;merchants&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;frontend developers&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;backend developers&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;devops&lt;/strong&gt;) die meer inzicht en expertise willen vergaren in het managen, ontwerpen en uitbreiden van hun Magento webshop. Kennis van Magento en bekendheid met programmeren worden verwacht bij het lezen van dit kookboek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Door het kookboek format hoeft het boek niet van begin tot eind gelezen te worden maar kunnen er bepaalde hoofdstukken/ recepten uitgekozen worden die interessant lijken. Het is erg breed van opzet. Installeren, configureren, creëren en optimaliseren van een Magento 2 omgeving komen aan bod. Het Magento 2 Cookbook bevat de volgende hoofdstukken: &lt;strong&gt;Install Magento 2 on Apache and Nginx&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Mangeto 2 system tools&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Enable performance in Magento 2&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Create catalog and categories&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Managing your store&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Creating a custom Magento 2 theme&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Create a Magento 2 extention (basics)&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Creating a Magento 2 extention (advanced)&lt;/strong&gt;. Meer informatie over de hoofdstukindeling vindt u &lt;a href=&quot;https://mage2cookbook.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Magento 2 Cookbook&quot;&gt;hier&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
      
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://localhost/2016/03/14/keystone-magento-2-magento-2-cookbook-door-ray-bogman-en-vladimir-kerkhof/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost/2016/03/14/keystone-magento-2-magento-2-cookbook-door-ray-bogman-en-vladimir-kerkhof/</guid>
      
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          <a title="Keystone Magento 2 Magento 2 Cookbook door Ray Bogman en Vladimir Kerkhof" href="http://localhost/2016/03/14/keystone-magento-2-magento-2-cookbook-door-ray-bogman-en-vladimir-kerkhof/">
            <img alt="Keystone Magento 2 Magento 2 Cookbook door Ray Bogman en Vladimir Kerkhof" src="http://localhost/img/news/mage2cookbook-small.jpg" />
          </a>
        ]]>
      </content>
      
    </item>
  
    <item>
      <title>Shoppimon Webinar: Making the move to Magento 2</title>
      
        <dc:creator>Ray Bogman</dc:creator>
      
      
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;box__image&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a title=&quot;Shoppimon Webinar: Making the move to Magento 2&quot; href=&quot;/2016/02/19/shoppimon-webinar-making-the-move-to-magento-2/&quot;&gt;
    &lt;amp-img noloading height=200 width=200 alt=&quot;Shoppimon Webinar: Making the move to Magento 2&quot; attribution=&quot;Shoppimon Webinar: Making the move to Magento 2&quot; layout=responsive src=&quot;/img/news/magento2-logo.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Overweegt u uw Magento webshop te migreren naar Magento 2?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Magento 2&lt;/strong&gt; is inmiddels al een tijdje beschikbaar. Men is te spreken over :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;check&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;De verbeterde Performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;De nieuwe niveaus qua compatibiliteit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;De flexibiliteit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maar betekent dit dat het tijd voor u is om 'over te stappen'?&lt;br&gt;We snappen dat het een enorme taak lijkt, en daarom is in samenwerking met Shoppimon deze &lt;strong&gt;webinar&lt;/strong&gt; georganiseerd, waar u meer inzicht kunt krijgen over de migratie naar &lt;strong&gt;Magento 2&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tijdens de webinar kunt u al uw &lt;strong&gt;Magento 2&lt;/strong&gt; vragen stellen en worden onder andere de onderstaande onderwerpen door de experts behandeld:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;check&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wanneer kan ik de stap nemen om naar Magento 2 te migreren?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hoe ziet het Magento 2 migratie proces eruit?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wat zijn de 'best practices' tijdens de Magento 2 migratie?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Welke problemen kan ik verwachten tijdens de Magento 2 migratie?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prestatie resultaten van Magento 2 sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wees erbij en u kunt de eerste zijn die mee doet aan &lt;strong&gt;Shoppimon's Closed Beta&lt;/strong&gt; voor &lt;strong&gt;Magento Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;box-info&quot;&gt;De aanwezigen maken ook nog kans op een exemplaar van Ray Bogman's aankomende boek &lt;a href=&quot;https://mage2cookbook.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Magento 2 Cookbook&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'Magento 2 Cookbook'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Planning:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;box-blank&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Datum : 24-02-2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tijd: 7:00 PM (CET)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://attendee.gotowebinar.com/register/7981565285081290242&quot; class=&quot;go-button button orange&quot;&gt;Registreer nu voor de webinar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://localhost/2016/02/19/shoppimon-webinar-making-the-move-to-magento-2/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost/2016/02/19/shoppimon-webinar-making-the-move-to-magento-2/</guid>
      
      <content type="html">
        <![CDATA[
          <a title="Shoppimon Webinar: Making the move to Magento 2" href="http://localhost/2016/02/19/shoppimon-webinar-making-the-move-to-magento-2/">
            <img alt="Shoppimon Webinar: Making the move to Magento 2" src="http://localhost/img/news/magento2-logo.png" />
          </a>
        ]]>
      </content>
      
    </item>
  
    <item>
      <title>Magento 1.8 CE binnenkort beschikbaar</title>
      
        <dc:creator>Ray Bogman</dc:creator>
      
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;De &lt;strong&gt;Magento 1.8&lt;/strong&gt; release was één van de hoogtepunten welke tijdens het Magento Imagine eCommerce congres te Las Vegas gisteren bekend is gemaakt. Magento 1.8 zal binnen twee weken beschikbaar zijn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Met de komst van &lt;strong&gt;Magento 1.8 &lt;/strong&gt;is het bijna een jaar geleden dat &lt;strong&gt;Magento 1.7&lt;/strong&gt; beschikbaar kwam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Magento 1.13 Enterprise&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Naast de nieuwe &lt;strong&gt;Magento 1.8 Community Edition&lt;/strong&gt; Release zal vanaf a.s. woensdag ook een nieuwe Magento Enterprise editie verschijnen, nl. Magento Enterprise 1.13.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Een opsommig van de nieuwe functionalieiten zal snel volgen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;check&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;meer dan 100 bugs opgelost&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Redis standaard in Magento Enterprise 1.13&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Een van de belangrijkste vernieuwingen binnen &lt;strong&gt;Magento Enterprise 1.13&lt;/strong&gt; is toch wel &lt;strong&gt;Redis&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Redis&lt;/strong&gt; is een &lt;strong&gt;key-value storage caching&lt;/strong&gt; toepassing welke de huidige &lt;strong&gt;Magento caching&lt;/strong&gt; toepassing dan ook volledig kan vervangen.&lt;br&gt;Binnen de &lt;strong&gt;Magento Redis&lt;/strong&gt; toepassing is het mogelijk alle caching data zoals: 'block', 'config' en 'sessions' in een Redis database op te slaan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Redis voor Magento Community Editie&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Binnen &lt;strong&gt;SupportDesk&lt;/strong&gt; gebruiken wij deze &lt;strong&gt;Redis&lt;/strong&gt; toepassing al enige tijd in de Magento Community Editie. En het wordt bij vele klanten als positief ervaren. De snelheidswinst is gemiddeld boven de 50%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zie hier een voorbeeld van een &lt;strong&gt;Redis Magento&lt;/strong&gt; website van een van onze klanten: [&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wildhibiscus.nl/&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wildhibiscus.nl/&quot; title=&quot;Wild Hibiscus&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.wildhibiscus.nl/&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Officieel is nog niet bekend wanneer Magento de Community Editie zal ondersteunen met Redis, dus maken wij voorlopig nog gebruik van een custom configuratie.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://localhost/2013/04/09/magento-18/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost/2013/04/09/magento-18/</guid>
      
    </item>
  
</channel>
</rss>
